

Kenrick Frans Robin Halff Curriculum Vitae

A software developer models the real world to solve real problems and create a fitting and accessible interface. Technology has exploded past decades and we don't know how to evolve with it. My mission is to solve problems, not causing them. Listening, understanding, testing and learning is the best way to achieve this.

- > Contact <u>kenrickhalff@gmail.com</u>
- > Portfolio <u>kenrickhalff-com.vercel.app</u>
- > Born November 5th 1993

$NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN$

EDUCATION

> MBO Utrecht Media

Application, Media & Game Development 2012 - 2016 MBO Niveau 4

> Hogeschool Utrecht

HBO Applied Computer Science 2018 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

> Logaholic BV

Ellermanstraat 15, 1099 BW Amsterdam Stagiaire / Junior Web Developer Feb 2013 - Jan 2014

- Data visualization
- Magento 1 store with integrated subscription options

> Bizzmark

Vreeswijksestraatweg 22, 3432 NA Nieuwegein Stagiaire / Junior Fullstack Developer Aug 2014 - Jun 2015 & Jan - Jul 2016

- Custom WordPress themes & design
- MyBizzMail, made with React, Redux & Node/Express rest API

NOTABLE WORK

> Websites / Apps

<u>kenrickhalff-com.vercel.app</u> <u>casual-happiness.vercel.com</u> <u>vnfkd.nl</u>

> Games

<u>kennyomg.itch.io/corona-shopper</u> JBL Speaker Catcher

> Jouw Omgeving

Maliebaan 79, 3581 CG Utrecht React Developer Jun 2015 - Jan 2016

 Worked on Jouw Omgeving tools in Django & React

> Comsys & Livecom

Laan Blussé van Oud Alblas 2a, 3769 AT Soesterberg Javascript Developer Feb 2017 - Sep 2017

- Angular 1 & Java Spring
- Modernizing old web interfaces (Comsys Dashboard, Livecom webchat & knowledgebank
- Research & consultancy for new development in tech

SKILLS

> Languages

TS, JS, Python, C++, C#, PHP, Java, SQL, GraphQL, FaunaQL

> Framework / Engine

React, Next, WP, Express, Django, Unity3d, Phalcon, SFML

> Professional

OOP, FP, UX, TDD, Agile, Scrum, Lean

> Social Brothers

Europalaan 100, 3526 KS Utrecht Frontend Developer Oct 2019 - Jun 2020

- Building and maintaining custom WordPress themes.
- E-commerce & SEO

> Casual Development

Lage Naarderweg 28B, 1211 AB Hilversum Founder

Apr 2018 - Now

- Psychology driven
- Lean Startup
- Gamification with the Octalysis Framework
- Nextls, Typescript & FaunaDB
- TDD